20th May 1993
20th May 1993
Yogi: Passport, they are just give it one minute
Yogi: Pasaport, sadece bir dakika lütfen
Passport just one minute
Pasaport sadece bir dakika
She is making the trip to the...
(anlaşılmıyor) 'ya yolculuk yapıyor.
Thank you very much, thank you.
Çok teşekkür ederim, teşekkür ederim.
What about your passort?
Peki ya senin pasaportun?
Yogi: They are there. They are there.
Yogi: ​Ayrıntılara bakın 31 / 5.000 Çeviri sonuçları Çeviri sonucu Onlar oradalar.
Turkish Yogi: Ms. Neşe, We can take passports and pass.
Turkish Yogi: Neşe Hanım, pasaportları alıp  geçebiliriz.
Guido: I have the passport. I have. I have.
Guido: Pasaportum var, var.
Yogi: Ah, you have it.
Yogi: Ah, sizin var.
Turkish Yogi: Can we pass to the passport control?
Turkish Yogi: Biz geçebilir miyiz pasaport kısmına?
Airport personell: Who are you?
Airport personell: Kim kimsiniz?
Turkish Yogi: All, there are 3 of us.
Turkish Yogi: Hepsi, 3 kişiyiz.
Airport personell: I'm doing it right now
Airport personell: Hemen alalım.
Turkish Yogi: OK, let's go directly to the passport.
Turkish Yogi: Tamam direkt pasaporttan geçelim.
They will come, they will come in 5 minutes.
Onlar gelir, 5 dakikaya gelir.
Turkish Yogi: They are all there.
Turkish Yogi: Hepsi orada.
I am coming back.
Geri dönüyorum.
You must know, also there are so many babies there also.
Bilmelisiniz ki, orada bir sürü bebek de var.
May God bless you.
Tanrı sizi korusun.
Flowers are really (pleasant?)
Çiçekler gerçekten (hoş?)
Everyone has so crying, you know.
Herkes çok ağlıyor biliyorsunuz.
She was the marriages and ...
O evliliklerdi vs...
So crying.
Çok ağlıyor.
Yogini: such a miracle, Mother.
Yogini:Ne büyük bir mucize anne.
Really? But I don't know the their names even
Gerçekten mi? Ama isimlerini bile bilmiyorum
Yogi: Katia (???)
Yogi: (Katia?)
Write to me, or to her.
Bana yaz ya da o yazsın.
like to ....
sanki ....
Airport personell: Come in side.
Airport personell: İçeri geçelim.
Really!
Gerçekten mi!
Can we?
Geçebilir miyiz?
All right, Bye bye
Elbette, Güle güle
Yogi: Thank you so much, Mother.
Yogi: Çok teşekkür ederiz anne.